Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
LAUNDRY HUB
What the heck?
Don't move. or else we all die!
Get down!
Get in the cart.
Watch out!
Come in.
So. what happened?
Well…
They got away.
FINALE
Head to the stairs.
Hold on.
What are you doing here?
Oh. you're here to save me.
Hey. Park Gang Seong.
Number 66 is on our side now.
Put down your gun.
I heard the person
who got my brother killed…
was you.
What…
What are you talking about?
I told you Park Yeong Gwang was killed
by the South Korean bastards
-during a mission--
-Didn't you say 66 killed him?
No. what I meant was…
Why are you so quiet?
Go ahead and say it wasn't you.
I…
couldn't save your brother.
That's it.
Move.
I said move!
You think doing this will keep you safe?
You betrayed the Party's orders as well!
I'll talk to the South Korean authorities.
You and I can defect together
-and find a way to live--
-Shut up!
Let me ask you one thing.
Why are you protecting that enemy bastard?
Sang-a.
It's okay.
To protect my daughter.
Protecting the people I care about…
is more important…
than killing my enemy.
You'll get another chance.
Trust me and walk away.
Hurry up and get in!
I was told to move the truck.
so I had to circle around.
What's going on?
Mr. Kim.
Let it through.
SECURITY CHECK
I heard gunshots. and it sounded serious.
Did something happen?
No. it's nothing serious.
It's just an internal issue.
-You can leave.
-But I have more laundry to pick up.
You can do it next time.
Please leave for now.
We have an urgent situation.
-Okay. then. Good night.
-Good night.
Close the barricades.
You can get out now.
-Take him to a hospital.
-What?
But a gunshot wound
is hard to keep under wraps.
Contact General Jang. He'll help.
What happened to Mr. Sung Han-soo
and Mr. Park Jin-cheol?
I saw them
getting into Ju Gang-chan's car.
-Ju Gang-chan?
-Yeah.
Han-soo.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
Kim. I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim?
Let's go.
Are you really not going to tell us?
Take him to a hospital.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
If you don't come…
the kids will die.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I'll be right there.
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
A FEW HOURS AGO
Who are you?
Damn it. I just mopped the floor.
-It's him.
-This is a Taekwondo studio.
Take off your shoes first.
-Whip it up. whip it up. up and down
-Whip it up
-Whip it up. whip it up
Whip it…
What the hell?
Are you Da-bin?
Yes. that's me.
Who are you?
Take him.
Mister.
Why are you doing this to us?
Please let us go.
Untie us right now!
Mister.
please let us go.
Please!
JUHAK CONSTRUCTION CHAIRMAN JU GANG-CHAN
Ready. sir.
So you're willing to risk your life
for your friends' kids.
I have to say I'm surprised.
Then again. you two did the same.
Now you get to choose.
Will you kill your friend…
or will you kill your kids?
I'm really sorry…
for dragging you into this.
If 66 dies. the kids will live.
Do you really have a choice?
-No!
-Da-bin!
-Stop!
-Dad!
-Father!
Dad. please help!
Father…
I'll do whatever you want. so stop it!
Kim.
Jin-cheol.
Han-soo.
You have to take me down…
for the kids to live.
Get it together!
Get up.
Kim!
There must be a way.
Focus on the kids.
Focus!
Han-soo!
Kim.
This is a bit of a letdown.
You're not taking this seriously.
I'll give you five minutes.
If you don't kill him by then.
I'll shoot the kids myself.
Father!
-Dad!
-Then I'll shoot 66.
Please help!
Father.
-Dad!
-Father!
Father…
What are you waiting for?
Your kids are calling for you.
Dad!
-Father!
-Dad!
More. more. more!
Get up.
Get up! I said get up!
Get up!
Tae-hun…
and Da-bin…
You have to save them.
And…
please take care…
of Min-ji.
How sad.
you're going to miss Min-ji so much.
Come back.
I'll wait for you.
You'll come back.
You're my dad.
One.
Two.
Three.
-Dad!
-Uncle!
Four.
-Damn it.
-Get up.
Get up! I said get up!
Three seconds.
Three seconds is enough.
-Da-bin!
-Dad!
Dad. you got shot. Are you okay?
-I'm okay. I didn't get shot.
-Are you okay?
I'm fine.
-I dodged it.
-Oh. you did?
-You didn't get shot?
-No. I didn't.
Are you okay? You must've been so scared.
-My poor Da-bin!
-Dad. I'm fine.
-If anything had happened to you…
-I said I'm fine!
Hurry up and free me.
Jeez. this is so annoying.
-That hurts!
-Stop touching my hair!
I won't touch your hair.
You're okay. you're okay.
Yeah. I'm fine.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-Can you get up?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Kim!
You okay?
What about the kids?
-They're fine.
-Are you okay?
What do you think?
Of course. he's not okay.
Right. you got beaten up by us. after all.
It took four seconds.
That's why he got shot.
It just grazed me.
-You okay?
-What do you think?
Of course. he's not okay.
He seems okay.
Hey. chairman.
We have some unfinished business.
A parent meeting.
What else is there to do?
I have to keep my promise.
Are you okay to drive?
I guess he is.
What about the kids?
Shouldn't we keep an eye on them
so they don't go out?
Does Tae-hun ever listen to you?
Of course. he doesn't.
He even attacks his own father.
At least Da-bin doesn't attack me.
She just ignores me.
We should leave them with someone
who can intimidate them.
-Like who?
-I know someone.
Someone scarier than me.
Actually. they might be
the scariest person on the planet.
Let's go.
Man. my legs.
My poor legs.
My legs are killing me.
My steering wheel!
Come on!
SECURITY COMMANDER KANG JI-YEONG
Is this a joke?
17TH AMPHIBIOUS MOBILE BRIGADE
RED DRAGON UNIT SPECIAL SECURITY BATTALION
Honey…
Would you mind
watching the kids for a bit?
If you could keep them in a room
and protect them for a few days…
Please?
This isn't a daycare center.
You little punk!
This is fake. Do you have any guns. lady?
I told you not to call me that.
Be quiet and go away.
Mom. lend me your phone.
Da-bin. be quiet.
I told you not to get into trouble.
I didn't get into trouble.
I just felt so bad for Kim
that I had no choice but to help.
I had no choice
because Jin-cheol told me to help.
Kim? Again?
I ought to just…
That's not true.
It's not true. honey.
I wanted to help him.
It was my choice.
My friend…
had to do one last mission
to see his daughter again.
So I wanted to help him.
Me too.
Still. you shouldn't have
put the kids in danger.
I'm sorry. honey.
I'm sorry too.
The kids will stay with me.
I can't trust you two.
-Honey!
I mean. Ji-yeong.
When will you middle-aged men grow up?
Seriously. when will you…
When…
Honey.
Have I told you
-that I love--
-Get out.
-Yes. he has.
-Let's go.
-Hurry.
-Sit properly.
Eat as much as you can in one sitting.
and don't ask for snacks.
-You know what to do. right?
-What?
And don't ask
for the Wi-Fi password. okay?
-Why?
-Don't ask. Just be quiet.
-Got it?
-Yeah. just go already.
-Don't make her mad.
-Okay. okay.
All right. attention!
Salute!
Hands down.
Dad.
Do as she says.
Are you hungry?
Yes. I am.
Those guys didn't even feed you?
What do you want?
Want me to order jjajangmyeon?
INTER-KOREAN GOVERNMENT TALKS
I'm pleased that both sides
could come to an agreement.
I hope that the North and the South
can move toward a cooperative future
through the free-trade zone.
Likewise.
Thank you. everyone.
Can the two of you please shake hands?
I think we have other matters to discuss.
About what happened last night. that is.
As you know.
we've done our best to accommodate
the North's requests during this visit.
Don't you agree?
It was all for the good
of inter-Korean cooperation.
What are your thoughts. sir?
But you know.
I think what happened last night
was out of line.
Shouldn't you take responsibility
for causing such a scene
on South Korean soil?
That was…
There was an internal issue.
And that issue
almost turned South Korea
into a battlefield.
No. we had no intention of--
Now. now.
Considering the outcome of these talks.
we won't take official retaliatory action
against the North.
However.
let's settle this with the understanding
that we have zero responsibility
for the casualties on your side.
Understood.
WE WELCOME THE NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION
TO JUHAK HERITAGE RESORT
Listen carefully.
The Party will be told that Ri Eung Ryeong
and 66 have been summarily executed.
If word gets out that we lost them
after the South handed them over to us.
we're all going to have to
take responsibility.
I've already spoken
with the delegation officials.
so make sure to keep your men quiet.
Understand?
Yes. sir.
-What are you talking about?
-Over there.
That's a person. right?
-What the heck?
-What is that?
That's a person. for crying out loud!
-Contact EMS and call for backup.
-Yes. sir.
-Sir. stay right here.
-Okay.
MYEONGJIN CENTRAL HOSPITAL
VIP1
UNIDENTIFIED PERSON
Goodness. Director General.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Start recording.
What's the rush?
Quickly. quickly.
This is how it is in the South.
You should get used to it too.
All right. then.
Let's start with the status of the ICBMs.
I have one last condition.
A condition?
After I give you all the information.
send me to Macau for asylum.
I'll think about it
depending on the quality
of the information.
So our understanding
is that the Strategic Rocket Force
is structured around a three-axis system.
Cholsan County. North Pyongan Province.
Chonchon County. Chagang Province.
And Kilju County. North Hamgyong Province.
At least 12 transporter erector launchers
are currently in service.
What about the current range?
Not only can they easily reach Guam.
but Alaska
and the US West Coast
are also within striking range.
How are they handling the fuel transition?
It's liquid-based right now.
but they're currently transitioning over
to solid fuel.
That's why I'm needed.
You see. all the information
is right in here.
VIP1
UNIDENTIFIED PERSON
PATIENT TRANSPORT
You kept your promise.
What are you going to do?
I'll take it from here.
It'd be a shame
to finish off an enemy so easily.
I need you to do one last thing for me.
No matter what happens.
promise me you'll survive.
What are you doing?
If you're done. go.
I wish you and your daughter…
a good life.
I'll stay alive too.
Good.
Stay alive…
no matter what.
COMMANDER'S OFFICE
CHEONSAN UNIT
So?
Who kidnapped Ri Eung Ryeong?
We have yet to identify the suspect. sir.
We're currently analyzing CCTV footage.
and we'll mobilize a team
once we track their movements.
Forget it. Let it go.
Sir?
We got all the information
we needed out of him.
It'd be a waste of taxpayer money
to keep him around longer.
It doesn't matter
whether he smuggles himself
out of the country or drops dead.
Either way. it's for the better.
But still…
Just do as I say.
That's an order.
Is this Macau?
Shit.
THE SEAS OF OUR HOMELAND
DO NOT TOLERATE LIES
THE COASTLINE IS THE FRONT LINE
OF NATIONAL DEFENSE!
No. it can't be.
F****** hell!
Don't move!
Stay right there!
-Stop!
-Stop right there!
Stop!
Stop right there!
JUHAK CONSTRUCTION CO.. LTD.
CHO PYEONG-GYEON
It's me. sir.
Hey.
My goodness. Are you alive and well?
What made you call me all of a sudden?
I called to ask you a favor.
A favor?
What is it?
I need you to dissolve
Juhak Construction.
Goodness.
You haven't called in over a decade.
and that's what you ask me for?
It has to do with my daughter.
Please. sir.
My goodness. that poor thing.
Good heavens.
She must be really big now.
She's pretty like her mom. right?
I understand.
I've known her since she was born. so…
Juhak Construction. huh?
All right.
You got it.
Thank you.
Just wait a few days.
Juhak Construction is nothing.
I'll chop it up like a cucumber
and make a salad out of it.
You know this will cost you. right?
We're close. but we're professionals.
so I won't lower my fees.
You understand. right?
-Yes. I do.
-Good.
All right. then.
I'll call you back.
Thank you. sir.
Prosecutors have conducted
a surprise search and seizure
at Juhak Construction headquarters
and its affiliates earlier this morning.
-What's your business here?
-The investigation team
-We have a search and seizure warrant.
-is looking into suspicious cash flows
of tens of billions of won
between Juhak Construction affiliates
and political figures.
The said team believes the repeated.
large-scale fund transfers
were not legitimate business transactions
and is now tracing their source
and where they were ultimately used.
This investigation
was reportedly triggered
after the Financial Intelligence Unit
filed suspicious transaction reports
with the prosecution late last year.
Do you acknowledge the bribery charges?
Are the claims of redevelopment bias true?
-Please answer. Assemblyman!
-Let me pass.
-Please comment!
-We can do this another time.
Are you going on a trip abroad
after selling out your country?
-Arrest him.
-Yes. sir.
Let go of me!
Let go!
CAMBODIA
A court has issued an arrest warrant
for Chairman Ju Gang-chan
of Juhak Construction
on charges of kidnapping. murder.
and threatening national security.
The court cited the severity of the crimes
and the risk of evidence tampering
for its decision.
Chairman Ju
is reportedly hospitalized in Seoul.
Meanwhile. the prosecution has stated
it'll expand the investigation to include
the company's founding history
and the chairman's illegal activities.
Hye-ri. I know what you did.
Do you know Kim Min-ji?
Dang. the police came by the school.
-I heard his daughter left the country.
-Daughter of a murderer.
-Interpol is after you too.
-She's going to prison with her dad.
Ju Hye-ri is screwed.
He's coming out!
When did you start making contact
with North Korea?
Are the murder allegations true?
Are you aware that your daughter.
who fled abroad. has been arrested?
-Please say something!
-A comment. please!
Say something. asshole.
How've you been?
How does it feel
to get taken down by a dog?
You pulled out my teeth.
but I still have my claws. you bastard!
You should've returned
as soon as the mission was over.
Where have you been
looking like that?
Didn't you miss your daughter?
I had some business to take care of
for Min-ji's sake.
So?
Is the business taken care of?
Yes.
It's all over now.
Then it's time for me
to wrap things up as well.
Number 66…
must die.
The body of a man with a gunshot wound
was discovered by an herb collector
in the woods near the resort
where the North Korean delegation
was staying.
The deceased has been identified
as a man in his forties. surnamed Kim.
and police have launched an investigation
into the exact circumstances of his death.
BODY WITH GUNSHOT WOUND DISCOVERED
NEAR NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION LODGING
DECEASED IDENTIFIED AS MAN IN HIS FORTIES
INVESTIGATION UNDERWAY
HIGH-PROFILE WANTED FUGITIVE
COMPREHENSIVE PROFILE
YOUNGER YEARS
ESTIMATED CURRENT APPEARANCE
DELETE THIS PROFILE?
NO / YES
THE LATE KIM. THE LATE IM YU-JIN
I'm back.
I'm not going to run into your arms.
That'd be too cheesy.
You knew?
Sang-a told me.
She said you died.
But that you'd come back alive.
I promise
never to leave you again.
I'll always…
be right by your side.
Dad…
Do you know how worried I was?
I was so afraid
something had happened to you.
Thank you for coming back.
It's okay.
Wow. the flowers are so pretty.
I should come visit Mom more often.
Did Mom like flowers too?
Yeah.
Maybe that's why I'm pretty.
No.
You're pretty
because you take after your mom.
You're right.
I definitely don't get my looks from you.
Jeez.
What happens to us now?
From now on.
we're going to live completely new lives.
We'll live in a new place
with new identities.
We'll even have new names.
I see.
But I still want you to call me Min-ji.
Why? You don't want to change your name?
Mom gave me that name.
Okay. I will.
It feels like
we have our own little secret.
Doesn't it?
It won't be easy starting a new life.
Will you be okay?
I think it'll be fun.
This life wasn't much fun anyway.
I'll just consider this a new beginning.
Then how about a new beginning
as a model student?
You can study hard and go to college.
What?
Why do you get to decide that?
You don't even know what I want to become.
I can start learning now.
What do you want to be. Min-ji?
Me?
Maybe a singer?
What?
If you take after me.
singing isn't your thing.
What do you mean?
I'm tone-deaf!
Is that funny?
My gosh.
Mr. Kim.
And Min-ji.
Those are your new identities.
There's a manual inside the file.
so learn it inside and out.
Especially you. Min-ji.
"Kim Ji-min"?
You didn't even bother trying. did you?
Well. coming up with new names
isn't our job.
Thank you.
I hope I never see your face again.
Likewise.
I don't really want to
see your face either.
Me too.
What?
I've never seen you smile before. Mr. Kim.
This is him cracking up.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Here.
What is it?
I hope you grow up to be
someone great and admirable.
I guess it's kind of pretty.
Thank you.
He's much warmer than he seems.
We chose that together.
The three of you bought a single hairpin?
It's an expensive one.
-Do you like it?
-Yeah.
-Get back to work.
-Right.
-Yes. sir.
Mr. Kim!
Kim!
Take this.
It's not much.
It's to prevent bad luck.
I thought a new suit would be fitting
for your fresh start.
Wow. you're so lucky. Dad.
Come on. take it. It's heavy.
Thank you.
Iron out the wrinkles in your suit.
and the wrinkles in life
will iron themselves out.
I'll remember that.
Goodness. I wonder
when I'll get to see you again.
By the way.
we lived in the same neighborhood
but never even knew each other's names.
My name is
Im Ho-won.
Kim…
-Nice to meet you.
-Likewise.
Please take care.
-Take care.
-You too.
Goodbye. then.
ECOLOGICAL PARK
-Min-ji.
-Yeah?
Should we listen to some music?
PLAYLIST FOR CHERRY BLOSSOM DAYS
You know. people say you need new clothes
for a fresh start.
Shouldn't I get
some new clothes too. then?
Yeah. I should.
I'm unemployed now.
But you'll get a new job. right?
Come on.
All right.
I'll buy you new clothes when I get a job.
That's a promise. right?
I'm going to ask for something
really expensive.
All right.
Your homeroom teacher is awful.
How could he not even wish you good luck
when you're transferring?
I heard things have been tense at school
because of Hye-ri.
Yeah. I saw on social media that people
are calling it a school for criminals.
I know.
I guess
you're really transferring.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
If only I hadn't messaged you that day…
You didn't do it on purpose.
It's okay.
Then…
Will you…
message me after you transfer?
I'll visit you.
I don't think
I can.
Right.
-I see.
-I'm sorry.
No. don't be sorry.
I think I should get going.
Already?
She's waiting for me.
Take care.
Here.
KIM MIN-JI
Will you…
remember my name?
Yeah.
Kim Min-ji.
How did it go?
Let's go.
This is it. What do you think?
Oh my gosh. it's so pretty!
-Come on. let's go.
-All right.
Hey. Kim!
Uncle?
-Hey.
Hey. what a great house.
Is it a rental or did you buy it?
Min-ji. did you do well on your exams?
Of course.
She's a level eight.
Wow. level eight?
-I'm jealous.
-What about Da-bin?
-She's healthy.
-That's all that matters.
Hey. Kim.
Hey. why are there so many boxes?
Do we have to move all of this?
Oh my.
Hey.
So you do own other clothes.
You look great.
I told you I have a lot of clothes.
-You look really rich.
-Do I?
Hey. hold on.
We're moving boxes.
and you came dressed like that?
Yeah.
Why?
Well. you know. it's a special day.
Have you lost your mind?
Be honest. You wore this
to avoid working. didn't you?
I'm tired. Stop talking to me.
You're tired?
Eat one of these. get an energy boost.
and start moving boxes.
And one for each of you
before you get to work.
Here.
And one for me too.
This tastes just like coffee.
It's good.
Just how many of those
do you have at home?
-Do you want a box?
-I sure do.
Are you moving in or not?
Coming!
Hey. let's finish up quickly and go eat.
-Hurry up and unload.
-Get a move on!
-Here we go.
-Let's go.
-Move some boxes. punk.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-Quickly. quickly.
-What are you doing?
-Hurry up now.
-Hurry up!
All right. here we go.
-That's the last one. right?
-Yeah.
Yeah. you little weasel.
You didn't even lift a finger.
All you did was carry the light boxes.
How can you look Min-ji in the eye?
Hey. Kim Min-ji-min… Ji-min.
Why are you laughing?
Do you want to see me get hurt
while carrying heavy boxes?
No. of course not.
Let's go eat. I'll take care of the rest.
Why bother? Let's just order jjajangmyeon.
-Jjajangmyeon is the best on moving days.
-Hey.
Why do you get to choose the menu?
Eat whatever Min-ji wants to have.
What do you want. Min-ji? You decide.
-Jjajangmyeon sounds good to--
-Did you say sushi? Okay.
Sushi sounds great.
Your daughter wants sushi.
You must really like sushi.
-Yeah. I love it.
-See?
Let's go have sushi.
-Get changed first.
-Let's go change.
-Han-soo. you're really something else.
-Okay.
You know. come to think of it.
you always wear the same outfit.
What are you looking at?
Darn it. I can't see without my glasses.
Hey. I want to see.
-Let me take a look.
-You can just look at that.
Oh. it's all here.
-Thank you.
-Gosh. there are so many items.
My stomach will be full of fish
swimming around.
Hey. Kim Min-ji-min.
You made a spectacular choice.
Order whatever you want.
-What are you having?
-I think I'll have--
Can we get one flounder…
Actually. make it five. What else?
Don't be shy.
And can we get five plates
of yellowfin tuna belly?
Here. have salmon. You like it. right?
You like it too.
One more salmon. please.
Make it five. please.
Do you want some too?
-Of course.
-Actually. make it ten.
Why are you eating with your hands?
That's how you eat sushi.
There's no eel here. what a shame.
Is it good?
Yeah. it's dangerously good.
He wasn't asking you. Uncle.
Sorry.
It's good.
Eat up.
-Okay.
Eat up. you guys.
Okay.
-Sir. you forgot the monkfish liver.
-What else do you want?
A new neighborhood. a new school…
and a new name I don't like.
Min-ji. come have breakfast!
Kim Min-ji!
I'm late.
A lot of things have changed.
but my dad and I haven't changed
all that much.
I'll eat after I get back. Save me some.
Okay. I will.
Be safe.
And don't get into any fights!
I won't!
Except for my dad laughing more often now.
Hello. ma'am.
Pure hearts. pure manners.
Join Pure Taekwondo.
-And my uncles are still the same.
-We're offering free trial classes.
Thank you.
Hello.
-Look who's back.
-We're offering free trial classes.
-Who's that man over there?
-It's not on the flyer.
but we play dodgeball.
and there are prizes. so come by. okay?
-Hello. ma'am.
-Cross slowly!
Please cross the street now.
Pure Taekwondo
is located on the third floor.
Feel free to drop by
during the free trial period.
Hello. ma'am.
Should we stop him?
Leave him be. It's a nice sight.
I bet he was a big club-goer.
POLICE
The weather is so nice.
I know. right?
It was really cold not too long ago.
-Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
Let's eat.
This looks good.
Hold on. We need to take a photo.
Sang-a hangs out with me sometimes.
Sang-a.
You're here to keep an eye on me. right?
No. I'm not.
You think you're special?
No.
Who saved your life?
You did.
Then who should you be thanking?
You?
So who should pay for this?
Right. I should pay.
Dig in.
Thank you.
How are things with your dad?
Is he more affectionate than before?
No. he's still the same.
Right.
That's not really who he is. is it?
It's totally not him.
Any good news lately. Sang-a?
-He was like. "You can't date yet."
-Really?
I'm not surprised.
Allow me to present today's special.
These would be good for when I do this.
Do you have regular glasses
instead of sunglasses?
Who are you?
I usually don't show this to anyone.
but here goes.
"Brother Monkey. what's gotten into you?"
Hello.
My name is Kim. Nice to meet you.
In my opinion. this case is…
Rock and roll.
Hey. Han-soo. Jin-cheol.
You think Min-ji will approve?
Probably not.
Hey. what do you think?
They suit me. right?
-You look weird.
Damn it.
Just kidding.
You look like Tony Leung Chiu-wai.
Tony Leung Chiu-wai. my foot.
He looks like a brewery owner.
Hey. you look like a middle-aged man
desperate to look young.
That's what we are.
Right.
We're middle-aged men.
Middle-aged men with glasses.
Now that I'm wearing glasses again
after a while.
I feel like
they're weighing my shoulders down.
Should we take them off?
No. It's better to be
middle-aged men with glasses.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Goodbye. sir.
-Oh. goodbye.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Have a good day.
-Take care.
-There wasn't much to choose from.
-You tried on 145 pairs.
It feels pretty good
to wear new glasses though.
Yeah. I feel like I could fly!
Hey. mister.
You should never mess with
middle-aged men with glasses.
-Yeah. someone could get someone hurt.
-Who?
The one who messed with them
or the middle-aged men with glasses?
I'm not sure.
All dads in the world
are just regular people.
-They work to support their families.
-What's with the color?
-and they're afraid of moms.
-Guys. check it out.
-And sometimes after work…
-Did you ask for these?
They're transition lenses.
-…they come home with smelly feet.
-I didn't ask for these though.
They give off a middle-aged man vibe.
Man. these are slick.
It may be hard to believe. but my dad
is also just a regular middle-aged man.
Well.
as long as no one messes with me.
HAPPINESS ROAD. HAENGBOK-RO
BAEKHO LABOR AGENCY
Oh. I almost forgot.
I think my dad's getting a new job.
Someone he knew back in the day
introduced him to it.
Juhak Construction is nothing.
I'll chop it up like a cucumber
and make a salad out of it.
You know this will cost you. right?
3RD FLOOR
May I help you?
Excuse me.
I'm here for an interview--
Check and check!
I just checked your résumé. Kim!
But you know.
I'm not sure if I can trust this.
Now then.
Shall we start
the interview?
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
STAY TUNED FOR A BONUS SCENE
BONUS SCENE
IN 2006. THERE WAS A FAMOUS TRIO
IN THE CHEONSAN UNIT
CHEONSAN
Korea's iron teeth!
They're unbreakable!
PARK JIN-CHEOL
YOON KYUNG-HO
SUNG HAN-SOO
CHOI DAE-HOON
KIM
SO JI-SUB
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
Subtitle translation by:
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm